Agus Andri Putra

Front End Developer



Personal Info

Email

andriputra.job@gmail.com

Address

Perumahan Cipadung Residence No.10 Rt.02 Rw.15 Kel.Cipadung Kec.Cibiru Kota Bandung

Phone

085795580512

Portfolio

www.eltaziky.com

Date of Birth

Tasikmalaya. Nov 06, 1988

Skill

HTML		100%
CSS		100%
Wordpress		90%
PHP	80%	
Javascript+JQuery	80%	
Wordpress		90%
Slicing		100%
Photoshop	85	5%

I am a professional web developer. My expertise is in the field of front-end and beautifying the website interface is my style. Not only that, slicing graphic designs into HTML, CSS, Javascript, and jQuery codes is another expertise that helps me in beautifying a website's interface. There are many past projects I've done so far, especially WordPress-based websites. I am also a full stack WordPress developer, working as a freelancer or full timer.

Experience

Aug 2016 - present

Front End Developer

PT. Lunaria Annua Teknologi / koinworks.com

- Slice PSD to HTML code
- UI code with CSS
- User Experience
- Good interaction to explore every page of the website
- Responsive website

Jan 2014 -May 2016

Web Developer

PT. Suntech Inti Perkasa / calibreworks.com

- Slice PSD to HTML code
- UI code with CSS
- User Experience
- Good interaction to explore every page of the website
- Responsive website
- Build a website with wordpress from scratch

Jan 2014 – Present

Wordpress Freelencer

Online Job

 Create a company profile website, ecommerce, Landing page with various online market clients, built using wordpress

Aug 2012 -May 2016

Lecturer in Computer Lab

State Islamic University Sunan Gunung Djati of Bandung

 Lecturer in Informatic Engineering Computer Lab, Practice Programming

May 2012 -Oct 2013

Digital Producer / IT Programmer

PT. Mediawave Interactive

 Drag data from all social media to be a material analysis of a product, trending topics, and conversations that are being discussed by netizens

Education

Aug 2007 -Jan 2012

State Islamic University Sunan Gunung Djati of Bandung

Faculty of Science and Technology / Informatic Engineering

- Bachelor Degree
- GPA: 3.33